<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bioinformatic Series on Remy-Ai&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>http://remy-ai.github.io/Bioinformatic/categories/bioinformatic-series/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Bioinformatic Series on Remy-Ai&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:16:43 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://remy-ai.github.io/Bioinformatic/categories/bioinformatic-series/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 3: Snakemake for RNA-sseq</title>
      <link>http://remy-ai.github.io/Bioinformatic/post/chapter3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 16:16:43 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://remy-ai.github.io/Bioinformatic/post/chapter3/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Snakemake is a python-based pipeline software that can be used to automate the workflow of bioinformatics analysis. In this chapter, we will use snakemake to build a RNA-seq analysis pipeline. Installation Install Miniconda Download the Miniconda installer for Linux from here Run the installer Add the following line to your .bashrc file 1 export PATH=&amp;#34;/home/username/miniconda3/bin:$PATH&amp;#34; Run the following command to update conda 1 conda update conda Install Snakemake 1 conda install -c bioconda -c conda-forge snakemake Pipeline Quality Control FastQC Input: Fastq files Output: FastQC report Command 1 fastqc -o {output} {input} 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 rule fastqc: input: &amp;#34;data/{sample}_1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter2: Linus &#43; Vim &#43; Tmux</title>
      <link>http://remy-ai.github.io/Bioinformatic/post/chapter2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 13:07:32 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://remy-ai.github.io/Bioinformatic/post/chapter2/</guid>
      <description>Basic commands of Linux ls : list files
ls -l : list files with details ls -a : list all files ls -al : list all files with details ls -lh : list files with details and size in human readable format ls -alh : list all files with details and size in human readable format cd : change directory
cd .. : change to parent directory cd ~ : change to home directory cd - : change to previous directory cd / : change to root directory cd PATH : change to PATH directory pwd : print working directory</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter1: what is bioinformatic in my view?</title>
      <link>http://remy-ai.github.io/Bioinformatic/post/chapter1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Oct 2022 14:49:04 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://remy-ai.github.io/Bioinformatic/post/chapter1/</guid>
      <description>Cores for bioinformattrue Coding + Statistcs + Biology Coding : Linux, Python, R, Perl, Shell, C++, Java, etc. Statistcs : Theory of probability, Statistics inference, Machine learning, etc. Biology : Principle of Neural Science, Gene XI, Molecular Biology of the Cell 6th, etc. Data analysis Data preprocessing and managment Data transformation and operation Mathematical model Data visualization Data summary Books Coding C++ Primer Python Crash Course Fluent Python Mr.Bird Linux Statistics All of Statistics Statistical inference Machine learning: A probabilistic Perspective Deep Learning Biology Genes IX Molecular biology of the cell Principle of Neurobiology Principle of Neural Science </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
